(Penny:)It's no problem.
Is everything okay?
(Sheldon:)I'm fine. It's just some
stomach medication for my trip.
(Sheldon:)There's the remote
yet distinct possibility
(Sheldon:)that I may end up
in South America.
(Penny:)Remember the old days when I
would've said something dumb
like, "Why?"
(Penny:)Uh, that doesn't sound good.
(Penny:)Remember the old days
when I used to point out
(Sheldon:)that your check engine light
was on?
(Sheldon:)-Yes.
-Get ready to go down memory lane.
(Sheldon:)-Penny, your check engine...
-Yeah, I know it's on, Sheldon!
(Penny:)Oh, no, no.
I cannot afford this right now.
(Sheldon:)Maybe it's just something minor.
(Sheldon:)Oh, good news,
the light just went out.
(Leonard:)Are we playing individual
or teams?